Guide to the Class of 1930, Yale College, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Class of 1930, Yale College, records
1930-1992
RU 26
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.75
The records consist of the files of Rollin G. Osterweis as reunion chairman and C. Colburn Hardy as secretary of the Yale College Class of 1930.
Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1930
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 10-A (YRG 10-A), Records of Yale College classes.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of a 1930 copy of The Bulldog, files of Rollin G. Osterweis as reunion chairman and C. Colburn Hardy as secretary of the Yale College Class of 1930.
Class reunions; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1930; Yale University -- Alumni and alumnae
- The Bulldog, 1930; Accession 19ND-A-473
  Conditions Governing Access
  The materials are open for research.
  - The Bulldog, 1930 (Box 1)
- Records of Rollin G. Osterweis as reunion chairman, 1942-1980; Accession 1983-A-082
  - Class news and letters, 1942-1944 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Class Organization and Scholarship Committee: Consolidation of Class of 1930 with 1930s, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Address list, 1948 April 20 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Bulldog, 25th reunion newspaper, 1955 June (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 35th reunion correspondence, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Bulldog, 35th reunion newspaper, 1965 June (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 40th reunion committee correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Bulldog, 40th reunion newspaper, 1948 April 20 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 45th reunion, files of the chairman, 1969-1975 (Box 1, Folder 9-11)
  - 45th reunion, stationery and programs, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 50th reunion correspondence, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - The Bulldog, 50th reunion newspaper, 1948 April 20 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Records of the class secretary, 1930-1992; Accession 1993-A-036
  - Records of the class secretary, 1930-1992 (Box 1)